(Sheldon:)but I would not leave
cash lying around.
(Scene:)Sheldon,
(Sheldon:)what do you think
you're doing?
(Sheldon:)My room is paid up
until the end of the month,
(Sheldon:)so I can do
with it whatever
(Sheldon:)I please, which includes
(Sheldon:)renting it out
for a dollar a night.
(Theodore:)It's like the '40s again.
(Sheldon:)Anyway, I'll leave you be.
I have to... oh, oh!
(Sheldon:)He's expecting a newspaper
in the morning.
(Sheldon:)Apparently,
they still make them.
(Penny:)All right, Sheldon,
this is over the line.
(Sheldon:)That's true,
(Sheldon:)but had I done
something under the line,
(Sheldon:)there wouldn't be a man
in your kitchen
(Sheldon:)who can't produce
a single form of ID.
(Theodore:)Oh, oh, I have a receipt
from a blood bank.
(Theodore:)I'm O-negative.
(Sheldon:)And now you know as much
about him as I do.
(Raj:)Oh, hey, Bernadette,
(Raj:)the swing comes
with two different mobiles.
(Raj:)The giraffes are pretty cute,
what do you think?
(Bernadette:)Great, go with the giraffes.
(Sheldon:)Although...